https://punklabs.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
At Punk Labs LLC, we take your privacy very seriously.
This Privacy Policy will define what personal information we collect from PunkLabs.com, and how that information is used.
Personal Information
Personal information is any information that identifies you as an individual.
If you contact us directly for any reason, we may keep a copy of that correspondence.
PunkLabs.com may also collect and log anonymous data including, but not limited to, the type of web browser and device you use, your device's unique ID and IP address, and information about the way you use PunkLabs.com. This information may be used to analyze and improve PunkLabs.com.
ChildrenWe do not knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us at contact@punklabs.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.
DisclosureWe will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any of the personal information you provide to us without your prior consent, except where required or allowable by law.
Security
Your personal information is stored offsite in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.
Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.
ChangesThis Privacy Policy may be updated in the future for any reason. The most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.
© Punk Labs LLC | Privacy | Contact | RSS
